Narrator: 2
Noun and adjective suffixes
a
Noun suffixes
M: accuracy
intimacy
Narrator: 2
F: marriage
storage
Narrator: 3
F: portrayal
survival
Narrator: 4
M: competence
fragrance
Narrator: 5
M: boredom
wisdom
Narrator: 6
F: idealism
racism
Narrator: 7
M: adversity
purity
Narrator: 8
F: achievement
treatment
Narrator: 9
F: stiffness
unpleasantness
Narrator: 10
M: censorship
ownership
Narrator: 11
M: inspiration
invasion
Narrator: b
Adjective suffixes
M: lovable
reversible
Narrator: 2
F: brutal
instrumental
Narrator: 3
F: picturesque
statuesque
Narrator: 4
M: soulful
truthful
Narrator: 5
M: catastrophic
metaphorical
Narrator: 6
F: glamorous
rebellious
Narrator: 7
M: childish
snobbish
Narrator: 8
F: attentive
oppressive
Narrator: 9
F: homeless
speechless
Narrator: 10
M: airy
Bloody